U.S. Manpower Administration "Manpower Daily Reporter" Newsletters 5380
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- February, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday February 9, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday February 8, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 7, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday February 6, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday February 5, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday February 2, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday February 1, 1968. Item is in English.
- March, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 29, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday March 28, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday March 27, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday March 26, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 25, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 22, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday March 21, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday March 20, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday March 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 18, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 15, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday March 14, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday March 12, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 11, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 8, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday March 7, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday March 6, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday March 5, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 4, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 1, 1968. Item is in English.
- April, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday April 26, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday April 25, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 24, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 23, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday April 22, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday April 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday April 18, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 17, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 16, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday April 15, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday April 12, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday April 11, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 10, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 9, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday April 5, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday April 4, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 3, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 2, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday April 1, 1968. Item is in English.
- May, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 31, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 29, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 28, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 27, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 24, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 23, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 22, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 21, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 20, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 17, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 16, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 15, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 14, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 13, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 10, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 9, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 8, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 7, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 6, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 3, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 2, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 1, 1968. Item is in English.
- June, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 28, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 27, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday June 26, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 25, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 24, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 21, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 20, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday June 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 18, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 17, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 14, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 13, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday June 12, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 11, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 10, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 7, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 6, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday June 5, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 4, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 3, 1968. Item is in English.
- July, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 31, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 30, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 29, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 26, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 25, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 24, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 23, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 22, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 18, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 17, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 16, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 15, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 12, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 11, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 10, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 9, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 8, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 5, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 3, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 2, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 1, 1968. Item is in English.
- August, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 30, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 29, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 28, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 26, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 23, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 22, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 21, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 20, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 16, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 15, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 14, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 13, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 12, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 9, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 8, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 7, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 6, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 5, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 2, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 1, 1968. Item is in English.
- September, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 30, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 27, 1968. Item is in English.